So as you can see, my biggest thing this week is deploy
the live call coach into two agencies. I'm going to do that
today.
So if I'm going to hit mark complete, it's basically saying, Hey,
how do I confirm this was done? I connected with both of
the agencies and made their accounts live.
How did it feel? Like a weight was lifted off my shoulders.
And now we hit more complete. Now, my one big thing is
done.
And if I go back to my Monday, I can see that
I did my four tasks. If I go back to Tuesday, I'm
still missing my strength training for legs this week.
Go back to Wednesday, I got them all done. Thursday, got them
all done. Today, I got two more things I got to get
done to get my points.
You only have to fill in the business days. The bonus days
are optional for Saturday and Sunday. They don't go towards any points,
but the goal is 20 points inside the week.
And then one big point for your one big thing. Now, if
you notice, I'm trying to always allocate things for each domain, each
day.
To make sure I'm feeding each domain. so you don't have to
do that. But to add things to your bench to eventually drag
and drop to this, you can just simply type here.
What's the action? Let's say, run 3 miles. I'm going to put
this inside a body. I can do a description if I want.
I'm going to choose body. And it's going to ask, do I
want to select a subdomain? And this would be for, for training.
And I'm going to hit create. Once that's created, you can see
it's over here. If I wanted to drag and drop this to
Saturday, I can drag and drop it to Saturday specifically.
And now once I get that done, I can check that box
off. And again, it's just a reminder piece for me, not a
manual.
That point piece. So it's very easy to do this and you're
going to be able to set this up automatically through your weekly
debrief session if you choose to take advantage of that on Sunday
evening or Monday morning to set up your entire week.